Guide to the President's Committee on Student Involvement in Decision Making records, 1968-1969.
President's Committee on Student Involvement in Decision Making records, 1968-1969.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
President's Committee on Student Involvement in Decision Making records, 1968-1969.
3-10-1284
Cornell University. President's Committee on Student Involvement in Decision Making.
.3 cubic ft.,
Membership lists, invoices, budgets, tape recordings, memoranda, bibliographies, printed material, correspondence, drafts, and reports.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes membership lists, invoices, budgets, tape recordings, memoranda, bibliographies, printed material, correspondence, drafts, and reports concerning the President's Commission, also known as the Morison Commission. Records primarily relate to student activism and involvement in university governance.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The President's Commission on Student Involvement in Decision Making was created by Cornell University President James A. Perkins in order to study student political activity at Cornell and its relationship to the educational and institutional operation of the University. Commission members included Jon Anderson, Mark Barlow, Sarah Diamont, Stephen Hadley, F. A. Long, Ian Macneil, Richard Marchase, Robert S. Miller, David Moore, Robert S. Morison, Raymond Thorpe, William Tomlinson, and Michael Wright.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes membership lists, invoices, budgets, tape recordings, memoranda, bibliographies, printed material, correspondence, drafts, and reports concerning the President's Commission, also known as the Morison Commission. Records primarily relate to student activism and involvement in university governance.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. President's Committee on Student Involvement in Decision Making.; Anderson, Jon.; Barlow, Mark.; Diamont, Sarah.; Hadley, Stephen.; Long, F. A.; Macneil, Ian.; Marchase, Richard.; Miller, Robert S.; Moore, David.; Morison, Robert S.; Thorpe, Raymond.; Tomlinson, William.; Wright, Michael.; Cornell University--Students.
Subjects:
College students--Political activity.; Self-government (in higher education)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
5" letter box:access restricted to permission of office of origin.
Tape recordings: access restricted in part.
CONTAINER LIST
- Chairman's Report, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Minutes and Other Meeting-related Material, Part 1, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Minutes and Other Meeting-related Material, Part 2, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Minutes and Other Meeting-related Material, Part 3, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Post-Sept. 1968 Minutes (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Post-Sept. 1968 Minutes, Oct. 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Post-Sept. 1968 Minutes, Nov. 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Post-Sept. 1968 Minutes, Dec. 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Post-Sept. 1968 Minutes, Jan. 1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Post-Sept. 1968 Minutes, Feb.-May 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Reports, Position, Accounts, Part 1, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Proposals and Drafts, Part 2, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Reports and Accounts, Part 3, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Accounts, Part 4, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Tape recordings
  - Morison Commission, 40th meeting, Feb. 10, 1969; tr. 3929
  - Mar. 12, 1968, tr. 3930
  - Mar. 13, 1968, tr. 3931
  - Mar. 18, 1968, tr. 3932
  - May 7, 1968, tr. 3933
  - Commission #12, July 24, 1968; tr. 3935
  - Commission #14, July 31, 1968; tr. 3936
  - Commission #15, Aug. 12, 1968; tr. 3937
  - Sept. 16, 1968, tr. 3938
  - Sept. 17, 1968, tr. 3939
  - Sept. 23, 1968, tr. 3940
  - Oct. 21, 1968, tr. 3941
  - Oct. 28, 1968, tr. 3942
  - Nov. 4, 1968, tr. 3943
  - Nov. 8, 1968, tr. 3944
  - Nov. 11, 1968, tr. 3945
  - Nov. 15, 1968, tr. 3946
  - Nov. 18, 1968, tr. 3947
  - Nov. 22, 1968, tr. 3948
  - Nov. 25, 1968, tr. 3949
  - Dec. 2, 1968, tr. 3950
  - Meetings 30, 31, Dec. 6 & 9, 1968; tr. 3951
  - Dec. 13, 1968, tr. 3952
  - Dec. 16, 1968, tr. 3953
  - Dec. 20, 1968, tr. 3954
  - Jan. 6, 1969, tr. 3955
  - Jan. 10, 1969, tr. 3956
  - Jan. 20, 1969, tr. 3957
  - tr. 3958
  - CU and Minutes, tr. 3959
  - Employment for Women, tr. 3960
  - Last mtg., tr. 3961
  - Morison Commission, tr. 3962